https://oatlands.org/privacy-policy/

Skip to main content Skip to footer
Who we are
Oatlands is a historic site of the National Trust for Historic Preservation. Oatlands is run by the corporation Oatlands, Inc. Our website address is: https://oatlands.org/.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
This website contains contact forms. Data provided in a contact form will be saved by Oatlands and shared with the appropriate partner. For example, a contact form inquiry about Teas will be shared with the partner that manages the Tea program.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Who we share your data with
Oatlands does not share your data.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
This website maintains a security certificate (https://)
This websites maintains a security program that maintains a firewall and brute-force attack protection.
This website does not store credit card numbers.
What data breach procedures we have in place
If Oatlands becomes aware of a data breach on this website, the affected parties will be notified as soon as possible.
What third parties we receive data from
This website uses products from third-party companies.
What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data
Oatlands uses shopping and polling data from this website to use for targeted marketing.
Industry regulatory disclosure requirements
Footer
V I S I T   O A T L A N D S
Garden & Grounds open 10:00 am – 5:00 pm daily. Purchase tickets here.
Guided Tours by appointment.
Last tour at 3:00 p.m.
Follow us!
Search this website
Your cart is currently empty.
Return to shop
×
